Good,now I was also thinking about some different materials that we haven't got in there at all.
很好。我还想到了一些我们这里没有的各种资源。
What do you think of the idea of introducing some workbooks?
你觉得引进一些练习册怎么样？
If we break them up into separate pages and laminate them, they'd be a great resource.
如果我们将它们拆分成单页，它们将是很好的资源。
The students could study the main course book in class and then do follow-up practice in the Self-Access Centre. That sounds good.
学生们可以在课堂上学习主要的教材知识，然后在自习室做后续的练习。听起来不错。
Okay,now finally we need to think about how the room is used.
好的，最后我们要想想怎么使用空间。
I'll have to talk to the teachers and make sure we can all reach some agreement on a timetable to supervise the centre after class.
我得跟老师们谈谈，确保在课后监督中心的时间上达成一致。
But we also need to think about security,too.Especially if we're going to invest in some new equipment.
但是我们也要考虑安全问题。特别是当我们对一些新设备投资时。
What about putting in an alarm?
装警报器怎么样？
Good idea.The other thing I'd like to do is talk to our technicians and see whether we could somehow limit the access to email.
好主意。我要做的另一件事是找到技术人员，看看能否减少电邮的使用。
I really don't want to see that resource misused.
我不想看到资源被滥用。
What about if we agree to only use it before and after class?
如果我们同意只在课前或课后用怎么样？
Yes,that would be fine.OK,anyway...that's great for now.
好的，没问题。好的，总之目前还不错。
We'll discuss it further when we've managed to...
我们将进一步讨论，当……